{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"0.376/4",
			"answer":"0.376/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"50.4/0.3",
			"answer":"50.4/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.28/0.0004",
			"answer":"6.28/0.0004",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.948/0.03",
			"answer":"0.948/0.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"42.8/0.04",
			"answer":"42.8/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.858/0.2",
			"answer":"0.858/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"52.4/0.4",
			"answer":"52.4/0.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"98.1/9",
			"answer":"98.1/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.65/0.5",
			"answer":"0.65/0.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.41/0.003",
			"answer":"1.41/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}